Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-31. Rules. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad
    - Civil Action No. 4594-51, 1952 (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - Rules Revision. Case No. A-2206, 1945-1947 (Box 326, Folder 12)
      1945-47.
    - Case No. A-1439, 1942-1947 (Box 326, Folder 13)
      1942-47.
    - 279-31 (a). Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1933-1943 (Box 326, Folder 14)
      1933-43.
    - Arbitration. Sunday Rule, 1931 (Box 326, Folder 15)
    - 279-31 (b). Mediation Agreement. C-811, 1930-1936 (Box 326, Folder 16)
      1930-36.
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1921-1927 (Box 326, Folder 17)
      1921-27.
  - Sub-Series 279-32. Rules. Chicago and Alton Railroad
    - Vacations, 1942-1947 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1928-1947 (Box 327, Folder 2)
      1928-47.
    - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1921-1926 (Box 327, Folder 3)
      1921-26.
  - Sub-Series 279-33. Rules. Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Company
    - 1958. Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 327, Folder 5)
      1951-55.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1955 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - General, 1949-1955 (Box 327, Folder 7)
      April 1949-55.
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Company, 1932-1949 (Box 327, Folder 8)
      1932-March 1949.
    - Vacations, 1942-1943 (Box 327, Folder 9)
      1942-43.
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 327, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-34. Rules. Pere Marquette District
    - 1946-November 1950 (Box 327, Folder 11)
    - 40-Hour Week. Ships' Clerks, 1949-1954 (Box 327, Folder 12)
      1949-54.
    - Exhibit No. 14,. Revenue Consolidation, 1958 (Box 327, Folder 13-15)
      1958 October 1
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 328, Folder 1)
      1948-50.
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 328, Folder 2)
      1942-49.
    - Rules Revision. Case No. A-2544, 1946-1948 (Box 328, Folder 3)
      1946-48.
    - Pere Marquette District, 1937-1945 (Box 328, Folder 4)
      1937-45.
    - Pere Marquette District, 1921 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Arbitration. Sunday Work, 1932 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Pere Marquette District, 1932-1936 (Box 328, Folder 7)
      1932-36.
    - Pere Marquette District, 1921-1929 (Box 328, Folder 8)
      1921-29.
    - Vacation Dispute. Grove, T.A., 1943-1947 (Box 328, Folder 9)
      1943-47.
    - Mediation Case No. A-5942, 1958-1959 (Box 328, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 328, Folder 11)
    - Teletype Machines. Mediation Cases Nos. A-2652, A-4489, 1947-1958 (Box 328, Folder 12)
      1947-58.
    - General, 1958-1962 (Box 328, Folder 13)
      1958-62.
    - General, 1955-1957 (Box 328, Folder 14)
      August 1955-57.
    - General, 1951-1955 (Box 328, Folder 15)
      September 1951-July 1955.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - December 1950-August 1951 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Agreements, 1947 (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-35. Rules. St. Louis and San Francisco Railway
    - 279-35 (Section 1). St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - 279-35 (Section 2). St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - 279-35 (Section 3). St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6997, 1962-1964 (Box 329, Folder 8)
      1962-64.
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1951-1962 (Box 329, Folder 9)
      1951-62.
    - 279-35 (Section 3). Revision. Mediation Case No. A-6764, 1962-1964 (Box 329, Folder 10)
      July 11, 1962-64.
    - 279-35 (Section 2). Revision. Mediation Case No. A-6764, 1961-1962 (Box 329, Folder 11)
      February 1961-July 10, 1962.
    - Mediation Case No. C-2382, 1955-1962 (Box 329, Folder 12)
    - 279-35 (Section 1). Revision. Mediation Case No. A-6764, 1958-1961 (Box 329, Folder 13)
      1958-January 1961.
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1956-1958 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1954-1957 (Box 330, Folder 2)
      1954-57.
    - Agreements, 1925 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - 1958. Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Case No. C-2144, 1953 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1952-1955 (Box 330, Folder 6)
      July 1952-55.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1953 (Box 330, Folder 7)
      1949-53.
    - General, 1950-1952 (Box 330, Folder 8)
      July 21, 1950-June 1952.
    - General, 1946-1950 (Box 330, Folder 9)
      1946-July 20, 1950.
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 330, Folder 10)
    - 279-35 (a). Married Women. Mediation Case No. A-480, 1941-1945 (Box 330, Folder 11)
      1941-45.
    - Case No. A-2857, 1948-1952 (Box 330, Folder 12)
      1948-52.
    - Case No. A-2462, 1946-1952 (Box 330, Folder 13)
      1946-52.
    - 279-35 (b-Section 2). Case No. A-930, 1942-1950 (Box 330, Folder 14)
      November 1942-50.
    - 279-35 (b-Section 1). Case No. A-930, 1941-1942 (Box 330, Folder 15)
      1941-October 1942.
    - 279-35 (a). Case No. A-738, 1930-1936 (Box 330, Folder 16)
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1942 (Box 330, Folder 17)
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railway, 1922-1929 (Box 330, Folder 18)
      1922-29.
  - Sub-Series 279-36. Rules. Kansas City Terminal Railway Company
    - Mediation Case No. A-7162, 1963-1966 (Box 330, Folder 19)
      1963-66.
    - Mediation Case No. A-7035, 1962-1966 (Box 330, Folder 20)
      1962-66.
    - Veterans Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1955-1957 (Box 331, Folder 1)
      1955-57.
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 331, Folder 2)
      1959-April 1962.
    - 279-36 (c). Ushers and Red Caps. Cases Nos. C-909 and R-107, 1934-1945 (Box 331, Folder 3)
      1934-45.
    - Kansas City Terminal Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - 279-36 (a). Mediation Cases Nos. A-1173 and A-1745, 1938-1944 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6863, 1959-1966 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 331, Folder 7)
      May 1962-63.
    - Union Shop. Check-Off. Mediation Case No. A-6549, 1957-1964 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6208, 1959-1960 (Box 331, Folder 10)
    - Red Caps. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 331, Folder 11)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5716, 1958-1959 (Box 331, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5715, 1957-1958 (Box 331, Folder 13)
    - Master Seniority Roster. Mediation Case No. A-5702, 1957-1958 (Box 331, Folder 14)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1950 (Box 331, Folder 15)
    - Mediation Case No. A-4941, 1955-1956 (Box 331, Folder 16)
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 331, Folder 17)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 331, Folder 18)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1954 (Box 331, Folder 19)
    - General, 1952-1956 (Box 331, Folder 20)
      May 4, 1952-56.
    - General, 1949-1952 (Box 331, Folder 21)
      1949-May 3, 1952.
    - Rule No. 1, 1939-1942 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. A-4346, 1953-1956 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Case No. A-3712, 1950-1952 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Case No. A-3522, 1950 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Case No. A-3283, 1949-1950 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Case No. A-3386, 1950 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Red Caps. 40-Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - General, 1945-1948 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - 279-36 (a). General, 1938-1944 (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - 279-36 (a). Kansas City Terminal Railway Company, 1934-1937 (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - Kansas City Terminal Railway Company, 1922-1929 (Box 332, Folder 12)
    - Vacation Dispute. Smith-Jackson, 1948 (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - Vacation Dispute. Usher Captains, 1945-1948 (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Vacation Dispute. Mailhandlers, 1947 (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Vacation Dispute. Lewis, et. al., 1945-1947 (Box 332, Folder 16)
    - Vacation Dispute. Holidays, 1945-1947 (Box 332, Folder 17)
    - Vacation Dispute. Checkmen, 1945-1947 (Box 332, Folder 18)
    - Vacation Dispute. Red Caps, 1945-1947 (Box 332, Folder 19)
    - Vacation Dispute. Lewis, et. al., 1944-1947 (Box 332, Folder 20)
    - Vacation Dispute. Countermen, 1943-1947 (Box 332, Folder 21)
    - Vacation Dispute. Mailhandlers, 1943-1947 (Box 332, Folder 22)
    - Vacation Dispute. Red Caps, 1942-1947 (Box 332, Folder 23)
    - Vacation Dispute. Holidays, 1942-1947 (Box 332, Folder 24)
    - Case No. A-2411, 1946 (Box 332, Folder 25)
    - Rules Revision. Case No. A-2336, 1944-1946 (Box 332, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-37. Rules. Union Depot Company, Columbus, Ohio
    - Union Depot Company, Columbus, Ohio, 1936-1952 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Case No. R-2099, 1948-1949 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - General, 1936-1956 (Box 333, Folder 3)
      May 27, 1936-56.
    - Agreements, 1935 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Case No. A-2971, 1948 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Union Depot Company, Columbus, Ohio, 1921-1923 (Box 333, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-38. Rules. New York Central Railroad
    - Health and Welfare, 1955-1959 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Eastern. Union Shop. Shea, J., 1958-1961 (Box 333, Folder 9-10)
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 333, Folder 11)
      September 1958-June 23, 1959.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 333, Folder 12)
      September 1957-August 1958.
    - General, 1952-1957 (Box 333, Folder 13)
      1952-September 1957.
    - General, 1949-1951 (Box 333, Folder 14)
    - General, 1947-1948 (Box 333, Folder 15)
    - General, 1962 (Box 333, Folder 16)
      September 20, 1962-December 1962.
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 333, Folder 17)
      September 1961-September 19, 1962.
    - General, 1960-1961 (Box 333, Folder 18)
      June 1960-August 1961.
    - Union Shop, 1953-1957 (Box 333, Folder 19)
      March 1953-57.
    - Union Shop, 1952-1953 (Box 334, Folder 1)
      November 1952-February 1953.
    - 40-Hour Week. Travel Time and Expenses, 1949-1958 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Eastern. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Western. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - National Mediation Board, Case No. 212. Vols. 1-4, 1956 (Box 334, Folder 5)
      May 3-8, 1956.
    - National Mediation Board, Case No. 212. Vols. 5-7, 1956 (Box 334, Folder 6)
      May 9-15, 1956.
    - 279-38 (Section 3). Agreements, 1963-1965 (Box 334, Folder 7)
      June 11, 1963-August 12, 1965.
    - 279-38 (Section 2). Mediation Case No. A-5395, 1961-1966 (Box 334, Folder 8)
      February 1961-66.
    - 279-38 (Section 1). Mediation Case No. A-5935, 1958-1961 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - General, 1964 (Box 334, Folder 10)
      August 18, 1964-December 1964.
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 334, Folder 11)
      November 1963-August 17, 1964.
    - Mediation Case No. A-6457, 1961-1964 (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6132, 1959-1964 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - 279-38 (Section 2). Agreements, 1960-1963 (Box 335, Folder 1)
      1960-April 26, 1963.
    - Sunday Operation of Transfer Stations. Exhibits, 1956 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6216, 1959-1962 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6450, 1959-1961 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 335, Folder 5)
      July 1959-May 1960.
    - Agreements, 1949-1959 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Western. Stolmeier, J.H., 1958-1959 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5626, 1957-1959 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6367, 1960-1962 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Cases Nos. 2-RC-9599, 2-RC-9652, and 2-RC-9739, 1958-1959 (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Building Service Employees International Union. Case No. 2-RC-9652, 1958-1959 (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Melrose Central Employees, 1958 (Box 335, Folder 12)
      1958 November 4
    - Eastern. Mediation Case No. A-5399, 1957-1959 (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - 7-Day Freight Transfer Operation, 1955-1957 (Box 335, Folder 14)
    - Rules Revision, 1947-1963 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - General, 1963 (Box 336, Folder 2)
      January-October 1963.
    - Union Shop. Eastman, H.H., 1952-1953 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1952 (Box 336, Folder 4)
      November 1951-October 1952.
    - Cases Nos. A-2830 and A-2650, 1947-1952 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Union Shop, 1951 (Box 336, Folder 6)
      February-October 1951.
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Arbitration Case No. A-2625. Testimony, 1948 (Box 336, Folder 8-9)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company. "New Mechanized Train Consist and Car Record System", 1947 (Box 336, Folder 10)
      1947 October 21
    - Emergency Board. Rules Changes Notices of Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1954 (Box 336, Folder 11)
      March 30, 1954-April 1, 1954.
    - 279-38 (Section 2). Eastern. Telegraphers' Case. Arbitration Case No. A-2625, 1948 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - 279-38 (Section 1). Eastern. Telegraphers' Case. Arbitration Case No. A-2625, 1948 (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - 279-38 (a). General, 1945-1946 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - 279-38 (a). General, 1940-1944 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - United States Board of Mediation. Case No. R-601-2, 1931 (Box 337, Folder 1)
      1931 February 3
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - 279-38 (Section 1). New York Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - 279-38 (Section 2). New York Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Western. Vacation Dispute. Overtime, Chicago Freight Station, 1948 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Western. Vacation Dispute. Overtime, Chicago Freight Station, 1946-1948 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - New York Central Railroad, 1940-1945 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Cases Nos. R-557 and R-558, 1923-1939 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - 279-38 (b). Stockyard Employees, Buffalo, New York. Case No. A-495, 1937-1943 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - 279-38 (c). Commissary and Dining Car Department. Cases Nos. R-673 and A-1120, 1937-1944 (Box 337, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-39. Rules. Alabama, Tennessee, and Northern Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Case No. R-2043, 1948-1955 (Box 337, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-40. Rules. Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company
    - Southern Pacific Company, Texas and Louisiana Lines, 1924-1926 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - Southern Pacific Company, Texas and Louisiana Lines, 1923 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - Case No. A-3801, 1950-1953 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 337, Folder 17)
    - 279-40 (b). Rules and Representation Disputes. Cases Nos. A-605 and R-555, 1939 (Box 337, Folder 18)
    - Briefs. United States Court of Appeals, Fifth Circuit, and United States Supreme Court, 1929 (Box 338, Folder 1-2)
    - Southern Pacific Company, Texas and Louisiana Lines, 1921-1922 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Case No. A-1762, 1944-1945 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1933-1940 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1929 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1941-1949 (Box 338, Folder 8)
      1941-March 1949.
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - General, 1956-1958 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - General, 1949-1955 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1930-1931 (Box 338, Folder 12)
      1930-June 1931.
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1927 (Box 338, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 338, Folder 14)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1954 (Box 338, Folder 15)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1931 (Box 338, Folder 16)
      1931 January
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1928 (Box 338, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-41. Rules. Boston and Albany Railroad
    - Eastern District -1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - 1959 Vacation and Holiday Movement (Box 339, Folder 2)
      May-September 1959.
    - Union Shop, 1952-1957 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1945-1957 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - General, 1958-1962 (Box 339, Folder 5)
      October 1958-62.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 339, Folder 6)
      1957-September 1958.
    - General, 1951-1956 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6410, 1959-1961 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1932-1950 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Vacations, 1941-1950 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Case No. A-1895, 1944-1946 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1921-1924 (Box 339, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-42. Rules. Minnesota Transfer Railway Company
    - General, 1945-1960 (Box 339, Folder 14)
      April 1945-60.
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 339, Folder 16)
    - Vacations, 1943-1949 (Box 339, Folder 17)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 339, Folder 18)
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company, 1930-1945 (Box 339, Folder 19)
      1930-March 1945.
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company, 1921 (Box 339, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-43. Rules. Spokane, Portland, and Seattle Railway Company
    - General, 1958-1962 (Box 339, Folder 21)
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 339, Folder 22)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 339, Folder 23)
    - Agreements, 1952-1953 (Box 339, Folder 24)
    - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle Railway Company, 1930-1955 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. C-2379, 1955-1956 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Case No. A-4080, 1951-1953 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Vacations, 1942 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - Agreement, 1940 (Box 340, Folder 6)
      1940 January 29
    - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle Railway Company, 1921-1924 (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-44. Rules. Columbia-Fidelity Transfer Company
    - Columbia-Fidelity Transfer Company, 1921-1922 (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-45. Rules. Lehigh and New England Railroad Company
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Case No. R-1388, 1944-1945 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - General, 1943-1952 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6294, 1960-1961 (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6290, 1960-1961 (Box 340, Folder 14)
    - Eastern. Agreements, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 15)
      1946 May 1
    - Mediation Cases A-6046 and C-2923, 1959 (Box 340, Folder 16)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 340, Folder 17)
    - General, 1953-1959 (Box 340, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-46. Rules. Texas Midland Railroad
    - Texas Midland Railroad, 1921 (Box 340, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-47. Rules. Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railway Company
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 340, Folder 20)
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railway Company, 1937-1946 (Box 340, Folder 21)
    - Veterans' Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1955-1957 (Box 340, Folder 22)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1950-1952 (Box 340, Folder 23)
    - Rules Changes, 1956 (Box 340, Folder 24)
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 340, Folder 25)
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railway Company, 1948-1956 (Box 340, Folder 26)
      April 11, 1948-56.
    - Agreement, 1947 (Box 340, Folder 27)
    - Rule No. 25. Case No. A-2549, 1947 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Cases Nos. A-1586, A-1847 and A-2061, 1943-1946 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railway Company, 1947-1948 (Box 341, Folder 4)
      1947-April 10, 1948.
    - Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, Separation Allowance. Mediation Case No. A-5239, 1956-1957 (Box 341, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-48. Rules. Norfolk Southern Railway Company
    - Arbitration Proceedings. Case No. A-747, 1942 (Box 341, Folder 6)
      1942 December 28
    - Agreements -1921-1950 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - 279-48 (a). General, 1941-1952 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk Southern Railway Company, 1935-1940 (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Rules Revision, 1951-1953 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1943-1947 (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Case No. A-1921, 1942-1945 (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - Agreement (Box 341, Folder 13)
    - 279-48 (b). Case No. A-747, 1941-1943 (Box 341, Folder 14)
    - Case No. A-747, 1944-1946 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6375, 1960-1961 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6532, 1961 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6253, 1959-1960 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - 279-48 (b). Case No. A-747. Exhibits, 1941-1943 (Box 342, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-49. Rules. Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad
    - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 342, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-50. Rules. Hocking Valley Railroad
    - 279-50 (a). Hocking Valley Division, 1934-1936 (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - 279-50 (b). Hocking Valley Division. Transfer of Personnel to Chesapeake and Ohio Railway General Offices, 1935-1937 (Box 342, Folder 10)
    - Hocking Valley Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 342, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-51. Rules. Toledo Terminal Railroad Company
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad Company, 1921-1950 (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 342, Folder 13)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 342, Folder 14)
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad Company, 1941-1943 (Box 342, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-52. Rules. St. Paul Union Depot Company
    - Mediation Case No. A-6389, 1960 (Box 342, Folder 16)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6189, 1960 (Box 342, Folder 17)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6342, 1960 (Box 342, Folder 18)
    - Lunchroom and Concessions. 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 342, Folder 19)
    - General, 1944-1952 (Box 342, Folder 20)
    - United Transport Service Employees of America, et. al. Case in United States Court of Appeals, District of Columbia, 1942 (Box 342, Folder 21)
    - 279-52 (b). Red Caps Representation Dispute. Case No. R-635, 1938-1943 (Box 342, Folder 22)
      1938-June 1943.
    - Vacations, 1942-1945 (Box 342, Folder 23)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 342, Folder 24)
    - Case No. R-1206, 1943-1945 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - 279-52 (b). Red Caps Representation Dispute. Case No. R-635, 1944-1946 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - 279-52 (b). Red Caps Representation Dispute. Case No. R-635, 1943 (Box 343, Folder 3)
      July-December 1943.
    - 279-52 (a). General, 1921-1943 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - 279-52. Rules. St. Paul Union Depot Company. Rules Revision. Case No. A-953, 1940-1944 (Box 343, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-53. Rules. Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway
    - General, 1956-1960 (Box 343, Folder 6)
      September 1956-60.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - General, 1944-1955 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Case No. A-4046, 1951-1955 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - Vacations, 1942-1950 (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - Vacation Dispute. National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1948-1949 (Box 343, Folder 13)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway, 1934-1943 (Box 343, Folder 14)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway, 1921 (Box 343, Folder 15)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway, 1921-1929 (Box 343, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-54. Rules. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railroad
    - Eastern. Mediation Case No. A-6248, 1959-1961 (Box 343, Folder 17)